const questionList = [
    {
        id: 1,
        question: "What is the name of Harry Potter's pet owl?",
        choices: ["Hedwig", "Ron", "Twig", "NightWing"],
        correctAnswer: "Hedwig",
    },
    {
        id: 2,
        question: "Who is Harry Potter's best (male) friend?",
        choices: ["Neville", "Ron", "Albus", "Draco"],
        correctAnswer: "Ron",
    },
    {
        id: 3,
        question: "Which Hogwarts House do Harry and his friends belong to?",
        choices: ["Hufflepuff", "Ravenclaw", "Slytherin", "Gryffindor"],
        correctAnswer: "Gryffindor",
    },
    {
        id: 4,
        question: "What platform is the Hogwarts Express located?",
        choices: [
            "Platform 9 and 1/2",
            "Platform 9 and 3/4",
            "Platform 10",
            "Platform 8 and 2/3",
        ],
        correctAnswer: "Platform 9 and 3/4",
    },
    {
        id: 5,
        question:
            "How old are you when you first receive your Hogwarts Letter?",
        choices: ["12", "13", "11", "15"],
        correctAnswer: "11",
    },
    {
        id: 6,
        question: "What is Harry Potter's middle name?",
        choices: ["Kirk", "Severus", "James", "Bilius"],
        correctAnswer: "James",
    },
    {
        id: 7,
        question: "What subject does Professor McGonagall teach?",
        choices: ["Flying", "Transfiguration", "Potions", "Charms"],
        correctAnswer: "Transfiguration",
    },
    {
        id: 8,
        question: "Where did Harry Potter's parents live (and die)?",
        choices: ["Frankfurt", "London", "Godrics Hollow", "Hogsmeade"],
        correctAnswer: "Godrics Hollow",
    },
    {
        id: 9,
        question: "What is the name of Ron Weasley's oldest sibling?",
        choices: ["George", "Charlie", "Fred", "Bill"],
        correctAnswer: "Bill",
    },
    {
        id: 10,
        question:
            "What is the name of the large, red, leather ball thrown and passed during a Quidditch match?",
        choices: ["Goober", "Snitch", "Bludger", "Quaffle"],
        correctAnswer: "Quaffle",
    },
    {
        id: 11,
        question:
            "Who was the woman killed by Tom Riddle for Helga Hufflepuff's Cup?",
        choices: [
            "Helena Hufflepuff IV",
            "Olivia Pendleton",
            "Hepzibah Smith",
            "Scarlet Grace",
        ],
        correctAnswer: "Hepzibah Smith",
    },
    {
        id: 12,
        question:
            "RAB was found in the fake locket at the end of book 6, who is RAB?",
        choices: [
            "Regulus Arcturus Black",
            "Remus Augustus Blaine",
            "Reginald Albus Brian",
            "Reina Anteck Blake",
        ],
        correctAnswer: "Regulus Arcturus Black",
    },
    {
        id: 13,
        question:
            "Who was the centaur that rescued Harry in the Forbidden Forest (book 1)?",
        choices: ["Buckbeak", "Groff", "Firenze", "Brutus"],
        correctAnswer: "Firenze",
    },
    {
        id: 14,
        question: "Who killed the Gray Lady?",
        choices: [
            "Salazar Slytherin",
            "The Bloody Baron",
            "Tom Riddle",
            "The Fat Friar",
        ],
        correctAnswer: "The Bloody Baron",
    },
    {
        id: 15,
        question: "Where did Tom Riddle intern for the summer months?",
        choices: [
            "Madame Malkins",
            "Olivanders",
            "The Three Broomsticks",
            "Borgin and Burkes",
        ],
        correctAnswer: "Borgin and Burkes",
    },
];

export default questionList;
